[{"answer": "Thank you for calling Best Buy Customer Service.  This is Jill.  Ho", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 14, "question": "", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": "Hi. I bought a stereo from you guys a few weeks ago and Im having som", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 18, "question": "Thank you for calling Best Buy Customer Service.  This is Jill.  Ho", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": "What seems to be the problem", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 22, "question": "Hi. I bought a stereo from you guys a few weeks ago and Im having som", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " Well, its not working properly.  The volume dial wont work and the CD tra", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 23, "question": "What seems to be the problem", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": "Im very sorry to hear that the stereo isnt working correctly, sir.  Hav", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Well, its not working properly.  The volume dial wont work and the CD tra", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Yes.  Ive tried that and it didnt do anything", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 31, "question": "Im very sorry to hear that the stereo isnt working correctly, sir.  Hav", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": "OK.  Well, at Best Buy we take pride in maintaining a reputation fo", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Yes.  Ive tried that and it didnt do anything", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Thank you", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 38, "question": "OK.  Well, at Best Buy we take pride in maintaining a reputation fo", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": "No problem.  Do you have the receipt for your stereo purchase", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Thank you", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": "Yes", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 40, "question": "No problem.  Do you have the receipt for your stereo purchase", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " OK.  Can you give me the date of purchase listed on it and the numbe", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 41, "question": "Yes", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Sure.  The date of purchase was July 19th, 2007 and the number printed o", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 45, "question": " OK.  Can you give me the date of purchase listed on it and the numbe", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": "Thank you for that information.  Are you able to look at the stereo at th", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Sure.  The date of purchase was July 19th, 2007 and the number printed o", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Sure.  Im right next to it", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 53, "question": "Thank you for that information.  Are you able to look at the stereo at th", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": "OK.  There should be a sticker on the back with a number.  Can yo", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Sure.  Im right next to it", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Lets see.  OK, I see it.  Its 8564312000125", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 58, "question": "OK.  There should be a sticker on the back with a number.  Can yo", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " All right.  Could you hold for just a moment, please", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Lets see.  OK, I see it.  Its 8564312000125", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " Sure", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 60, "question": " All right.  Could you hold for just a moment, please", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": "Thank you for holding, sir.  Im sorry, but the product you purchase", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Sure", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": "How can you tell", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Thank you for holding, sir.  Im sorry, but the product you purchase", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": "The number you gave me allows me to pull up information on you", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 66, "question": "How can you tell", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": "So what do I do now", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 71, "question": "The number you gave me allows me to pull up information on you", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": "The easiest option is just to bring your stereo, with your receipt, back t", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 72, "question": "So what do I do now", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " OK.  I can do that", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 77, "question": "The easiest option is just to bring your stereo, with your receipt, back t", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": "Just take the stereo to the customer service desk and the staff ther", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 78, "question": " OK.  I can do that", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " All right", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 84, "question": "Just take the stereo to the customer service desk and the staff ther", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": "Is there anything else I can do for you today", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 85, "question": " All right", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " No, that was it", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 86, "question": "Is there anything else I can do for you today", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " OK.  And again, on behalf of the Best Buy Company, we are very sorr", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 87, "question": " No, that was it", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " OK.  Thanks", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 91, "question": " OK.  And again, on behalf of the Best Buy Company, we are very sorr", "qSentId": 90},{"answer": "Have a nice day", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 92, "question": " OK.  Thanks", "qSentId": 91},{"answer": "Bye", "docId": "03-04", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Have a nice day", "qSentId": 92}]
